cryptocynews.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy - Bitcoin News

By visiting CryptocyNews.com you agree with and consent to the content in this privacy policy.

Certain areas of the CryptocyNews website involve personal data handling when this has been submitted by the user (including but not limited to competition forms and newsletter subscriptions). Data obtained will not be forwarded, sold or otherwise distributed to third parties.

Any Information obtained from competition or survey forms will not be published or communicated to third parties in any way; it will be used to communicate with the applicant regarding the results or otherwise of the specific campaign entered.

Personal information may also be obtained for analytical purposes such as traffic monitoring. Data obtained in this manner is used only for statistical analysis and monitoring.

If the is user subscribed can be unsubscribed at any time desired. If you are experiencing any problems with unsubscribing, please contact us to fix the issue asap.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **How we use cookies**

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, you can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. It helps us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

Third party vendors and ad networks may use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. Such use of a cookie enables advertisers to serve ads based on your visits to other sites on the Internet.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on January, 06, 2018. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes If you have any questions feel free to contact info@cryptocynews.com
